A little pink fish was all alone in the big sea.
Một chú cá hồng nhỏ ở một mình trong biển lớn.
There were no jellyfish, no starfish and no octopuses.
Không có sứa, không có sao biển và không có bạch tuộc.
The little pink fish was sad.
Chú cá hồng nhỏ buồn lắm.
It waited and it watched.
Nó đợi và nó nhìn.
Oh look! Here comes a fish!
Ồ nhìn kìa! Có một con cá đến!
The fish was big and grey.
Con cá to và xám.
It was bigger and fatter and longer and faster than the little pink fish.
Nó to hơn, béo hơn, dài hơn và nhanh hơn chú cá hồng nhỏ.
The little pink fish was scared.
Chú cá hồng nhỏ sợ hãi.
Oh look! Here comes another fish!
Ồ nhìn kìa! Có một con cá khác đến!
The fish was blue, green, yellow, orange, purple and red.
Con cá có màu xanh dương, xanh lá, vàng, cam, tím và đỏ.
It was the biggest fish of all.
Nó là con cá to nhất.
The little pink fish was very scared.
Chú cá hồng nhỏ rất sợ.
But look again little fish!
Nhưng nhìn lại đi cá nhỏ ơi!
It wasn't one big fish.
Đó không phải một con cá lớn.
It was lots of little fish, all different colours.
Đó là rất nhiều cá nhỏ, đủ màu sắc khác nhau.
Hey little pink fish! Don't be scared!
Này cá hồng nhỏ ơi! Đừng sợ!
Said a little fish.
Một con cá nhỏ nói.
Come with us!
Đi với chúng mình nào!
Now the little pink fish is happy.
Bây giờ chú cá hồng nhỏ vui rồi.
It always swims with its new friends and it's never scared.
Nó luôn bơi cùng bạn mới và không bao giờ sợ nữa.
Together is better, thinks the little pink fish.
Ở cùng nhau thì tốt hơn, chú cá hồng nhỏ nghĩ.